Guide to the International Association for Cultural Freedom Records 1941-1978
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Seminars, 1950-1977
  - Subseries 8: Milan 1955: The Future of Freedom, September 12-17
    - Transcript of Proceedings: September 17, afternoon session, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, A-B, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, C-E, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, F-G, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, H-I, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, J-K, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 9)
    - Speeches, L-O, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 10)
    - Speeches, P, 1955 (Box 398, Folder 11)
    - Speeches, R-Z, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 1)
    - Press Summary, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, September 12th Session, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, September 13th Session, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, September 14th Session, 1955 (Box 399, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, September 16th Session, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, September 17th Session, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, Belgian, English, 1955-1957 (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, French, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, French, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, German, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, Swiss, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, Painters' Conference, 1955 (Box 400, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, Painters' Conference, 1955 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Painters' Conference, Biographies, English, Belgian, French, 1955 (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Painters' Conference, Biographies, Dutch, Italian, Swiss, 1955 (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Painters' Conference, Biographies, 1955 (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Painters’ Conference, Programs, 1955 (Box 401, Folder 5)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters’ Exhibit, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 401, Folder 6)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, A-B, 1953-1956 (Box 401, Folder 7)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, C-D, 1953-1955 (Box 401, Folder 8)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, E-G, 1953-1955 (Box 401, Folder 9)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, H-L, 1953-1955 (Box 401, Folder 10)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, M-Q, 1953-1955 (Box 401, Folder 11)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, R, 1953-1955 (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Painters' Conference, Young Painters' Exhibit, S-Z, 1953-1955 (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Painters' Conference, Reaction to Exhibition, 1955-1956, for photographs see Series V (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 9: Paris 1956: Committee on Science and Freedom, Study Groups, August 28-September 1
    - Agenda for Seminar; Reports of Activities, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Papers, English, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Papers, English, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Papers, English, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 7)
    - Papers, French, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 8)
    - Papers, French, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 9)
    - Papers, French, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 10: Mexico City 1956: Cultural Freedom in the Western Hemisphere, September 18-26
    - Planning, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 11: Zurich 1956: Meeting of Literary Reviews, September 24-27
    - Report on the Conference, 1956 (Box 402, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 12: Tokyo 1957: Problems of Economic Growth, April 1-6
    - Correspondence, A-F, 1956-1957 (Box 402, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, G-L, 1956-1957 (Box 402, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, M-Q, 1956-1957 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, R-Z, 1956-1957 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Papers, 1957 Folder 4: Papers, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Papers, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Papers, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, April 9-17, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, April 5-8, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, April 3-4, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, March 29-April 2, 1957 (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Reviews and Magazines, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Reviews and Magazines, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and Magazines, 1957, for photographs see Series V (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 13: New York 1957: East-West Music Conference, Pilot Meeting, April 23-27
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 7)
    - Financial Records, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records, Nicholas Nabokov, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, Nicholas Nabokov, 1957 (Box 404, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 14: Oxford 1957: Changes in Soviet Society, June 24-29
    - Correspondence, A-E, 1956-1957 (Box 404, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, F, 1956-1959 (Box 404, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, G-K, 1956-1958 (Box 404, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, L-Q, 1956-1959 (Box 404, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, R-Z, 1957-1959 (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Planning, Participants, Programs, 1957 (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Papers, 1957 (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Papers, 1957 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Papers, 1957, for photographs, see Series V (Box 405, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 15: Dacca 1957: State Aid to the Arts, August 11
    - Bulletin, 1958 (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 16: Paris 1958: Roundtable Discussion of the Views of George Kennan
    - Booklet, The West, The Atom, and Russia, 1958 (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 17: Venice 1958: Tradition and Change in Music, September 16-23
    - Correspondence, General, 1957-1958 (Box 405, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, A-B, 1957-1958 (Box 405, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, C-L, 1957-1958 (Box 405, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, M-P, 1957-1958 (Box 405, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Q-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 405, Folder 12)
    - Planning, Programs, 1958 (Box 405, Folder 13)
    - Papers, 1958, for oversized items see Box 494 (Box 405, Folder 14)
    - Papers, 1958 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Patronage of the Arts, Correspondence, Plans for Study, 1958 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1957-1958, for photographs, see Series V (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Transcript of Proceedings, undated (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts (Box 406, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 18: Vienna 1958: Workers Participation in Management, September 19-25
    - Correspondence, General, 1958-1959 (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1958-1961 (Box 406, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, A-C, 1957-1959 (Box 406, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Chester, T.E., 1957-1958 (Box 406, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, D-K, 1958-1959 (Box 406, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, L-O, 1958-1959 (Box 406, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, P-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 406, Folder 12)
    - Invitations and Replies, A-C, 1958-1960 (Box 406, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Replies, D-G, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and Replies, H-M, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and Replies, N-S, 1958-1959 (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and Replies, T-Z, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Participants; Press Releases, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - Papers, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 6)
    - Papers, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 7)
    - Papers, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 8)
    - Papers, 1958 (Box 407, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 19: Rhodes 1958: Representative Governments and Public Liberties in the New States, October 6-13
    - Correspondence, Edward Shils, 1957-1958 (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Edward Shils, 1958-1959 (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Joanna Londos, 1957-1958 (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, A-C, 1958 (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, D-L, 1957-1959 (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, M-P, 1957-1959 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Q-Z, 1957-1959 (Box 408, Folder 7)
    - Planning, 1957-1959 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases; Programs, 1958 (Box 408, Folder 9)
    - List of Papers, undated (Box 408, Folder 10)
    - Draft, Edward Shils, undated (Box 408, Folder 11)
    - Background Papers, 1958 (Box 408, Folder 12)
    - Discussion Papers, English, 1958 (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Discussion Papers, English, 1958 (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Discussion Papers, French, 1958 (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Discussion Papers, Vietnamese, 1958-1959 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Summaries and Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 409, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1958, for photographs see Series V (Box 409, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 20: Ibadan 1959: Representative Government and National Progress, March 16-23
    - Planning, 1959 (Box 409, Folder 7)
    - Papers, 1959-1960, for photographs, see Series V (Box 409, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 21: Tunis 1959: Freedom and Responsibility: The Role of the Scholar in Society, April 13-18
    - Correspondence, Planning, 1958-1960 (Box 409, Folder 9)
    - Participant List, 1959 (Box 409, Folder 10)
    - Programs, 1959 (Box 409, Folder 11)
    - Opening Speeches, 1959 (Box 409, Folder 12)
    - Papers, English, 1959 (Box 409, Folder 13)
    - Papers, French, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 2)
    - Booklets, 1959, for photographs, see Series V (Box 410, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 22: Shiraz 1959: The Role of Intellectuals in Public Life, May 3-7
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (for photographs see Series V.C, Box 3:3) (Box 410, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 23: Vienna 1959: Young Painters of the Present, July 24-August 15
    - Correspondence, A, 1959-1960 (Box 410, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, B-G, 1958-1959 (Box 410, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, H-M, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, N-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 410, Folder 8)
    - Catalogue, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 24: Lourmarin 1959: Meeting in Lourmarin, July 8-13
    - Correspondence, France, A-H, 1958-1959 (Box 410, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, France, I-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 410, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Germany, 1958-1959 (Box 410, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Italy, 1959 (Box 410, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Portugal, Spain, 1958-1959 (Box 411, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, United States, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with Participants, A-E, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Participants, F-L, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with Participants, M-Z, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Participants, A-B, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with Participants, C-E, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Participants, F-L, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Participants, M-O, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Participants, P-Z, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, A-C, 1958-1959 (Box 411, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, D-H, 1958-1959 (Box 411, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, I-N, 1958-1959 (Box 411, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, O-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 411, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Administrative, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Contacts, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Organizations: Aix en Provence; Academie des, Arts et Belles Letteres; Amis de Lourmarin, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Hotels, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Hotels, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Films, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Observers, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 7)
    - Planning, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 8)
    - Programs, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 9)
    - Papers, undated (Box 412, Folder 10)
    - Papers, undated (Box 412, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1959, for photographs, see Series V for oversized items see Box 494 (Box 412, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 25: Basel 1959: Industrial Society and Western Political Dialogue, September 20-26
    - Correspondence, A, 1959-1961 (Box 412, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, B-C, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, D-G, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, H, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, I-K, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, L-O, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, P-S, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 5)
    - Planning; Participants; Program, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 6)
    - Papers, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 7)
    - Summary of Discussions; Text of Communiqué, 1959 (Box 413, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 26: Beirut 1960: Legal Services, February 1-5
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 413, Folder 9)
    - Papers, 1960, for photographs see Series V (Box 413, Folder 10)
    - Outline of Discussion, 1960 (Box 413, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 27: Khartoum 1960: Traditional Order and National Progress, February 15-21
    - Participants; Program; Paper, 1960 (Box 413, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 28: Karachi 1960: Education and Society, April 23-24
    - Participants, 1960 (Box 413, Folder 13)
    - Papers, undated (Box 413, Folder 14)
    - Papers, undated (Box 413, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 29: Dakar 1960: Press and Progress in West Africa, May 31-June 4
    - Correspondence, A-K, 1959-1960 (Box 413, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, L-Z, 1959-1961 (Box 414, Folder 1)
    - Planning, 1959 (Box 414, Folder 2)
    - Papers, 1960 (Box 414, Folder 3)
    - Report, 1960 (Box 414, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 30: Berlin 1960: Progress in Freedom, June 16-22
    - Correspondence, A-G, 1958-1960 (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, H-M, 1959-1960 (Box 414, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, N-Q, 1959-1960 (Box 414, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, R-S, 1958-1960 (Box 415, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 415, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, A, 1950-1960 (Box 415, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, B, 1959-1960 (Box 415, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, C-F, 1959-1960 (Box 415, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, G-H, 1959-1960 (Box 415, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, I-K, 1959-1960 (Box 415, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, L-M, 1959-1960 (Box 415, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, N-R, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, S, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Nabokov, A-E, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Nabokov, F-P, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Nabokov, Q-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Study Groups, Plenary Session, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Study Group I, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Study Group II, 1959-1960 (Box 416, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Study Group III, 1959-1960 (Box 417, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Study Group IV, 1959-1960 (Box 417, Folder 2)
    - Post Conference Correspondence, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 3)
    - Post Conference Correspondence, A-L, 1960-1961 (Box 417, Folder 4)
    - Post Conference Correspondence, M-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 417, Folder 5)
    - Telegrams, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 6)
    - Purpose of the Conference, 1959-1960 (Box 417, Folder 7)
    - Planning, 1950-1960 (Box 417, Folder 8)
    - Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 417, Folder 9)
    - Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 417, Folder 10)
    - Participants, 1959-1960 (Box 417, Folder 11)
    - Participant Biographies, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 12)
    - Program, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 13)
    - Program, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 14)
    - Poster, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 15)
    - List of Works sent to the Conference; List of Books and Pamphlets issued by the IACF, 1960 (Box 417, Folder 16)
    - Statements; Declaration; Proposed Modifications to Statutes, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 1)
    - Reports on Ten Years of Activity, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 3)
    - Papers, Study Group 1, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 4)
    - Papers, Study Group 2, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 5)
    - Papers, Study Group 3, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 6)
    - Papers, Study Group 4, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 7)
    - Papers, Study Group 1, French and Spanish, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 8)
    - Papers, Study Group 2, French, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 9)
    - Papers, Study Group 3, French, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 10)
    - Papers, Study Group 4, French, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 11)
    - Papers, Study Group 1, German, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 12)
    - Papers, Study Group 2, German, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 13)
    - Papers, Study Group 3, German, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 1)
    - Papers, Study Group 4, German, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 2)
    - Paper by Edouard Roditi, English, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1960 (Box 419, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 1960, for photographs see Series V (Box 419, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 31: Venice 1960: Fiftieth Anniversary of Tolstoy's Death, June 29-July 2
    - Correspondence, A-H, 1958-1959 (Box 419, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, I-P, 1959 (Box 419, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Q-Z, 1959 (Box 419, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, A-H, 1959-1960 (Box 419, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, I-M, 1959-1960 (Box 419, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, N-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 420, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Vittore Branca; Cini Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 420, Folder 2)
    - Planning, 1958-1960 (Box 420, Folder 3)
    - Participants, 1959-1960 (Box 420, Folder 4)
    - Program, 1960 (Box 420, Folder 5)
    - Papers, English, undated (Box 420, Folder 6)
    - Papers, English, undated (Box 420, Folder 7)
    - Papers, English, undated (Box 420, Folder 8)
    - Papers, English, undated (Box 420, Folder 9)
    - Papers, French, undated (Box 420, Folder 10)
    - Papers, French, 1960 (Box 420, Folder 11)
    - Papers, German and Italian, undated (Box 420, Folder 12)
    - Papers; transcript of proceedings, 1960 Folder 14: Papers; transcript of proceedings, 1960 (Box 420, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 32: Canberra 1960: Constitutionalism in Asia, August 22-26
    - Participants; Programs, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 1)
    - Papers, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 33: Copenhagen 1960: The Writer and the Welfare State, September 8-14
    - Correspondence, A, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, B, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, C, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, D-E, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, F, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, G, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, H, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, I-K, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, L-M, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, N-P, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Q-R, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, S, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1960 (Box 421, Folder 15)
    - Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 422, Folder 1)
    - Participants; Biographies, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Programs, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Papers, English, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Papers, French, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - Papers French, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, 1960, for photographs see Series V (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 34: Helsinki 1960: The Writer and Society, November 11-12 (local follow-up to Copenhagen Seminar)
    - Correspondence; Participants; Financial Report, 1960-1962 (Box 422, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 35: New Dehli 1960: Fiftieth Anniversary of Tolstoy's Death, December 6-8
    - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 422, Folder 12)
    - Papers, 1960 (Box 422, Folder 13)
    - Summaries of Discussion, 1960, for photographs see Series V (Box 422, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 36: Cairo 1960: The New Metropolis in the Arab World, December 17-22
    - Correspondence, A-E, 1959-1961 (Box 423, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, F-M, 1959-1961 (Box 423, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, N-Z, 1958-1961 (Box 423, Folder 3)
    - Planning, 1959-1961 (Box 423, Folder 4)
    - Participants, 1960 (Box 423, Folder 5)
    - Programs, 1960 (Box 423, Folder 6)
    - Papers, 1960 (Box 423, Folder 7)
    - Papers, 1960 (Box 423, Folder 8)
    - Press Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 423, Folder 9)
    - Paper Publications, 1960-1963 (Box 423, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 37: Poona 1961: Paths to Economic Growth, January 21-28
    - Correspondence, A-C, 1960-1962 (Box 423, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, D-G, 1960-1962 (Box 423, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, H-J, 1960-1962 (Box 424, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, K-L, 1960-1961 (Box 424, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, M-O, 1960-1961 (Box 424, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, P, 1960-1961 (Box 424, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, R-Z, 1960-1962, for photographs, see Series V (Box 424, Folder 5)
    - Planning; Participants; Programs, 1960-1961 (Box 424, Folder 6)
    - Synopsis of Subjects of Discussion, 1961 (Box 424, Folder 7)
    - Papers, 1961 (Box 424, Folder 8)
    - Papers, 1961 (Box 424, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 1961 (Box 424, Folder 10)
    - Follow-up Memorandum; Report; Press Clippings; Financial Reports, for photographs see Series V (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 38: Khartoum 1961: Tradition and Progress in Sudanese Society, January 23-28
    - Correspondence, A-R, 1958-1961 (Box 424, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, S-Z, 1958-1961 (Box 425, Folder 1)
    - Planning; Participants, 1959-1961 (Box 425, Folder 2)
    - Programs, 1961 (Box 425, Folder 3)
    - Papers, 1960-1961 (Box 425, Folder 4)
    - Papers, 1960-1961 (Box 425, Folder 5)
    - Papers, 1960-1961 (Box 425, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1961, for photographs see Series V (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 39: New Dehli 1961: South and South East Asia Have a Second Look at Democracy, February 1-8
    - Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 425, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 425, Folder 9)
    - Planning; Participants, 1960-1961 (Box 425, Folder 10)
    - Papers, 1961 (Box 425, Folder 11)
    - Report on Marion Bieber's Trip to India, 1961 (Box 426, Folder 1)
    - Statutes of the Afro-Asiatic Counsel, 1961-1962 (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - Financial records, 1960-1961 (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Financial records, 1960-1961 (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, 1961, for photographs see Series V (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 40: Tokyo 1961: East-West Music Encounter, April 17-May 6
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1956-1957 (Box 426, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, A-G, 1957-1959 (Box 426, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, H-O, 1957-1960 (Box 426, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, P-Z, 1957-1959 (Box 426, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Society for International Cultural Exchange, 1958-1959 (Box 426, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, A-G, 1958-1959 (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, H-P, 1959 (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Q-Z, 1959 (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, A-B, 1960-1962 (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, C-F, 1960-1961 (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, G-K, 1960-1961 (Box 427, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, L-Q, 1960-1961 (Box 427, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, R-S, 1960-1961 (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - Planning, 1956-1959 (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - Planning, 1957-1960 (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - Planning, 1961 (Box 428, Folder 5)